http://www.turfteam.com/privacy/

Privacy
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Equipment Locator and The Turf Team. Equipment Locator and The Turf Team promote the use of fair information practices. Because Equipment Locator and The Turf Team are committed to your privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE:
Equipment Locator is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Equipment Locator and The Turf Team will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Equipment Locator and The Turf Team collect information from our users at several different points on the web site.
Equipment QUOTE REQUESTS:
In order to obtain a Equipment price quote, a user must first complete a Quote Request Form. A user is required to give their contact information (such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address). This information is used to contact the user and provide the quote or other information that they have requested. It is optional for the user to provide financial information, but can be done so that The Turf Team can review and pre-qualify the user for financing if they are interested. All customer information obtained via the quote request form is encrypted for security purposes and stored on a secured server.
ORDERS:
Information is requested from the user on the e-Catalog order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If The Turf Team has trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. All customer information obtained via the order form is encrypted for security purposes and stored on a secured server.
COOKIES:
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For example, a cookie is used to store items during e-Catalog shopping so that a list of what you are ordering is maintained. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use the site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user, may not be able to use the e-Catalog shopping basket function on the site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the site.
LOG FILES:
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic and geographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
SHARING:
We may share demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is generally not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. However, Equipment Locator and/or The Turf Team may send E-mails or mail about special offers at the Dealership or other offers or information that may be of interest to the user based on the information we collect. The Turf Team uses an outside company (such as UPS, USPS, Fed Ex. etc.) to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not to our knowledge, retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.
LINKS:
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Equipment Locator and The Turf Team are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
SURVEY AND CONTESTS:
From time to time, our site requests information from users via surveys or may offer contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as zip code and age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES:
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
SECURITY:
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When our quote request or order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just "surfing".
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, has restricted access at Equipment Locator and at the dealership. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, order clerk, sales representative, or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Access to the information is made via a password-protected site. Each time an employee needs to access information, they must enter their password to gain access to the information. Furthermore, employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Employees are periodically notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected.
SUPPLEMENTATION OF INFORMATION:
In order for this web site to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it may be necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from third party sources.For example, to determine if customers qualify for financing, the dealership may use their name and social security number to request a credit report or approval from a lending institution.
SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES:
Equipment Locator and The Turf Team may send the user site and service announcement updates which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regard to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone.
CORRECTING / UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION:
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as address or E-mail), or if a user no longer desires to receive information from Equipment Locator and The Turf Team, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove that user's personal data from our database.
Contact Us
OUR LOCATION
4620 West US 6
| Morris, IL 60450
(815) 942-6620
View Map
HOURS OF OPERATION
Mon-Fr 8:00 AM - 4:30 PM
NEED A QUOTE?
Then let us get that for you
Fields with asterisks* are required.
The Turf Team Inc. © 2020 | All Rights Reserved Site by R.A. EquipmentLocator.com
GOT A QUESTION?
Let us help you get moving.
